mashnol.org 2019-04-07

# Privacy Policy - Mashnol

**PRIVACY POLICY**

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at mashnol.org@gmail.com.

At Mashnol.org, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by Mashnol.org and how it is used.

 **Log Files**

Like many other websites, Mashnol makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

 **Cookies and Web Beacons**

Mashnol uses cookies to store information about visitor preferences, record user-specific information on the pages the user accesses or visits, customize web page content based on visitor browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

 **Videos & Images**

All the Videos Embedded in our website “Mashnol.org” are taken from “Mashnol Youtube Channel” with the permission of its Actual Owner.

Some of the Images has been taken from “[https://stocksnap.io/”](https://stocksnap.io/%22) which provides Images under the Creative Commons CC0 license. That means you can copy, modify, distribute any photo on the site, even for commercial purposes, all without asking permission!
